A Guide to the Papers of the Virginia Quarterly Review, 1935-1954
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Weeks, Mangum 1934-1943, ca. 50 items (Box 133)
- Weelen, Jean-Edmond 1938-1939, 4 items (Box 133)
- Weems, Wharton 1929-1932, 5 items (Box 133)
- Weigel, Henrietta 1936-1953, 13 items (Box 133)
- Weigert, Hans 1943-1944, 13 items (Box 133)
- Weil, Leo 1929-1939, 15 items (Box 133)
- Weir, Charles, Jr. 1940-1951, 13 items (Box 133)
- Weir, Ernest 1939, 7 items (Box 133)
- Weisiger, Cary 1930-1934, 18 items (Box 133)
- Weismiller, Edward 1936-1940, 19 items (Box 133)
- Welch, Marie 1936-1937, 2 items (Box 133)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Welch
- Welles, Sumner 1944-1954, 27 items (Box 133)
- Wellington, Dorothy 1943-1947, 28 items (Box 133)
- Wells, Henry 1947-1950, 11 items (Box 133)
- Wells, Herbert George 1945 June 15, 1 l. (Box 133)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Wells
- Welty, Eudora 1937-1954, 7 items (Box 133)
- Wertenbaker, Charles 1935, 4 items (Box 133)
- Wertenbaker, Thomas Jefferson 1936, 2 items (Box 133)
- Wescott, Glenway 1941, 2 items (Box 134)
- West, Jessamyn 1942 March 16, 1 l. (Box 134)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to West
- West, Rebecca 1950 March 29, 1 l. (Box 134)
- Westfeldt, Kittie Monroe 1930, 4 items (Box 134)
- Westfeldt, Tuthe 1930, 2 items (Box 134)
- Weston, Christine 1953, 2 items (Box 134)
- Wheaton, Elizabeth 1941, 4 items (Box 134)
- Wheeler, Bernice 1939-1941, 10 items (Box 134)
- Wheeler, Burton 1935-1940, 5 items (Box 134)
- Wheeler-Bennett, John 1936-1953, ca. 50 items (Box 134)
- Wheelock, John Hall 1938-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 134)
- Wheelwright, John 1937-1938, 4 items (Box 134)
- Whicher, George 1951, 7 items (Box 134)
- Whipple, Maurine 1938-1939, 12 items (Box 134)
- Whistler, Laurence 1939, 3 items (Box 134)
- Whitaker, Arthur 1953-1954, 12 items (Box 134)
- White, E.B. 1937 January 8, 1 l. (Box 134)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to White
- White, Lynn, Jr. 1953, 3 items (Box 134)
- White, Nelia Gardner 1949, 4 items (Box 134)
- White, Walter 1942, 4 items (Box 134)
- White, W.H. Landon 1935, 2 items (Box 134)
- White, William Allen 1936-1943, 5 items (Box 134)
- White, William H., Jr. 1929-1939, 18 items (Box 134)
- Whitehill, Mrs. Morton 1940 April 24, 1 l. (Box 134)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Whitehill
- Whittlesey House 1941-1945, 5 items (Box 134)
- Wicker, Tom 1951-1952, 3 items (Box 134)
- Widdemer, Margaret 1953 July 8, 1 l. (Box 134)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Widdemer
- Wiener, Norbert 1952-1954, 4 items (Box 134)
- Wiggam, Lionel 1936, 9 items (Box 134)
- Wiggins, Robert 1951 March 20, 1 items (Box 134)
- Wilbur, Richard 1948, 6 items (Box 134)
- Wilds, Sophie 1938-1940, 5 items (Box 134)
- Wiley, Bell 1949-1954, 23 items (Box 134)
- Wilgus, Alva Curtis 1942, 12 items (Box 134)
- Wilkins, Michael 1944-1949, 18 items (Box 134)
- Willcox, William 1938-1954, 10 items (Box 134)
- Williams, Charles Seymour 1924-1937, 21 items (Box 134)
- Williams, James Peter, Jr. 1939-1941, 6 items (Box 134)
- Williams, Lewis 1929-1941, 15 items (Box 134)
- Williams, Murat 1940, 2 items (Box 134)
- Williams, Oscar 1937-1951, 23 items (Box 134)
- Williams, Stanley T. 1946-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 134)
- Williams, T. Harry 1954, 8 items (Box 134)
- Williams, Tennessee 1949 December 13, 1 l. (Box 134)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Williams
- Wilkie, Wendell 1942-1943, 4 items (Box 134)
- Willoughby, William 1949, 8 items (Box 134)
- Wilmer, Dr. and Mrs. William Holland 1924-1935, ca. 50 items (Box 134)
- Wilmot, Chester 1952, 4 items (Box 134)
- Wilson, Charles Morrow 1936-1941, 14 items (Box 134)
- Wilson, Edmund 1931-1942, 7 items (Box 134)
- H. W. Wilson Co. 1926-1949, ca. 50 items (Box 134)
- Wilson, James Southall 1936-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 134)
- Wilson, John Dover 1947 September 15, 1 l. (Box 134)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Wilson
- Wilson, Leon 1950, 2 items (Box 134)
- Wiltse, Charles 1937-1950, 18 items (Box 134)
- Wimsatt, William, Jr. 1949, 2 items (Box 134)
- Winant, John 1944-1947, 4 items (Box 135)
- Wing, Willis 1936-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 135)
- Wingfield, Marshall 1939, 2 items (Box 135)
- Winnacker, Rudolph August 1948-1952, 24 items (Box 135)
- Winner, Percy 1950 June 22, 1 l. (Box 135)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Winner
- Winslow, Anne 1949-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 135)
- Winters, Yvor 1936-1945, 3 items (Box 135)
- Wintringham, Mr. and Mrs. Tom 1946, 14 items (Box 135)
- Wise, Jennings 1941-1953, 4 items (Box 135)
- Wise, Stephen 1939, 11 items (Box 135)
- Wise, William 1950, 3 items (Box 135)
- Wish, Harvey 1950 September 22, 1 l. (Box 135)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Wish
- Withers, William 1945, 6 items (Box 135)
- Withington, Robert 1936-1953, 15 items (Box 135)
- Witte, Edwin 1951-1953, 16 items (Box 135)
- Wolf, Harriet 1945-1954, ca. 100 items (Box 135)
- Wolfe, Bertram 1941-1943, 5 items (Box 135)
- Wolfers, Arnold 1938 July 15, 1 l. (Box 135)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Wolfers
- Wood, Clement 1940-1943, 3 items (Box 135)
- Woodfin, Maude 1942-1946, 8 items (Box 135)
- Woodford, Jack 1941, 3 items (Box 135)
- Woodrum, Clifton 1936 December 16, 1 l. (Box 135)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Woodrum
- Woodward, C. Vann 1937-1954, 37 items (Box 135)
- Woody, T. Braxton 1939 December 1, 1 l. (Box 135)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Woody
- Woolf, Cecil 1951, 3 items (Box 135)
- Woollcott, Alexander 1935-1936, 2 items (Box 135)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Woollcott
- Wranek, William 1942 March 24, 2 l. (Box 135)
- Wright, Austin 1941-1951, 24 items (Box 135)
- Wright, Cuthbert 1936-1942, 18 items (Box 135)
- Wright, David McCord 1933-1950, 30 items (Box 135)
- Wright, Esmond 1950, 6 items (Box 135)
- Wright, Gordon 1953-1954, 16 items (Box 135)
- Wright, Louis 1936-1954, 31 items (Box 135)
- Wright, Quincy 1943-1945, 15 items (Box 135)
- Wright, Walter Livingston 1947-1948, 8 items (Box 135)
- Wriston, Henry 1951, 6 items (Box 135)
- Wroth, Lawrence 1950, 2 items (Box 135)
- Wurdemann, Audrey 1937, 2 items (Box 135)
- Wyatt, Edith Franklin 1949 April 16, 1 l. (Box 135)
- Wyllie, Irvin 1950-1952, 27 items (Box 135)
- Wyllie, John Cook 1936-1953, 7 items (Box 135)
- Wyndham, Horace 1942-1952, 6 items (Box 135)
- Wynn, Dudley 1935-1937, 22 items (Box 135)
- Wyzanski, Charles 1939, 2 items (Box 135)
- Miscellaneous W 1935-1954, ca. 1000 items (Box 136 & 137)
- Yalden-Thomson, David 1951-1952, 5 items (Box 137)
- Yale, William 1939-1949, 4 items (Box 137)
- Yale University Press 1928-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 137)
- Yates, Irene 1951-1954, 3 items (Box 137)
  TL(carbons), with Virginia Quarterly Review
- Yeats, William Butler 1938, 3 items (Box 137)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Yeats
- Yoseloff, Martin 1946, 2 items (Box 137)
- Young, Hugh 1924-1939, 17 items (Box 137)
- Young, Karl 1940-1941, 4 items (Box 137)
- Young, Marguerite 1940, 3 items (Box 137)
- Young, Owen 1939, 2 items (Box 137)
- Young, Stark 1936-1952, ca. 50 items (Box 137)
- Younger, Edward 1950-1954, 9 items (Box 137)
- Youtz, Philip 1938, 4 items (Box 137)
- Zabel, Morton 1952, 4 items (Box 137)
- Zaturenska, Marya 1936, 2 items (Box 137)
- Zehmer, George 1932-1953, 5 items (Box 137)
- Zigrosser, Carl 1939-1940, 31 items (Box 137)
- Zimmern, Alfred 1948, 12 items (Box 137)
- Zobell, Claude 1940, 3 items (Box 137)
- Zugsmith, Leane 1939, 3 items (Box 137)
- Miscellaneous X-Y-Z 1935-1954, ca. 150 items (Box 137)
- Miscellaneous manuscripts and pictures (Box 138 & 139)